gmanetwork.com 2003-10-01

# Welcome to iGMA.tv : The Corporate Website of GMA Network Inc.

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |   

  * About iGMA.tv
  * Contact Info
  * User Agreement
  * **Privacy Policy**

| 

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.iGMA.tv 

It is iGMA.tv's continuing goal to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information and user privacy practices. 

This website has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personal identification is collected from you through the website.
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**  
Information Collection and Use**

> iGMA.tv is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. iGMA.tv collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**  
Online surveys and promos**

> When iGMA.tv holds surveys or promos, users are sometimes required to give their contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest or to inform them if they have won in a certain contest or promo. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) and unique identifiers (such as social security number or driver's license number). 

**  
Cookies**

> Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**  
Log Files**

> We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**  
Sharing**

> We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
> 
> These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.   
  
---|---  
|  |   
| 

**Links**

> This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that iGMA.tv is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**  
Notification of changes**

> If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
  
---|---  
  
|  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|
